[
  {
    "question": "Which Disney movie did NOT debut in the 90's?",
    "choices": ["Tarzan", "Beauty & the Beast", "The Little Mermaid", "The Lion King"],
    "correct": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a pog?",
    "choices": ["A pig", "Pollen Smog", "Music genre", "Piece in a game played"],
    "correct": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the top grossing film of the 1990's?",
    "choices": ["Titanic", "Forrest Gump", "Independence Day", "Home Alone"],
    "correct": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "NASAâ€™s Hubble Space Telescope was launched in 1990 on what space shuttle?",
    "choices": ["Challenger", "Discovery", "Atlantis", "Endeavor"],
    "correct": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who did former President Bill Clinton have an affair with?",
    "choices": ["His Wife", "Monica Lewinsky", "Brooke Shields", "Ann Kelly"],
    "correct": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which person from Friends was known for their sarcastic behavior?",
    "choices": ["Phoebe", "Chandler", "Ross", "Rachel"],
    "correct": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of the early instant messenger service?",
    "choices": ["Netscape Navigator", "Safari", "Google Chat", "AIM"],
    "correct": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was known as The Dream in NBA?",
    "choices": ["Johnson", "Hakeem", "Hubert", "Lebrone"],
    "correct": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who plays the lead role in Home Alone?",
    "choices": ["Macaulay Culkin", "Bruce Jenner", "Sean Penn", "Christopher Walken"],
    "correct": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Wayne's World, who is Wayne's best friend?",
    "choices": ["Jamey", "Winston", "Garth", "Samson"],
    "correct": "2"
  }
]